Ownership of ji Rayaka Hello, please
update the mentioned points, hey
proud people, the market is
not ready to stop, but it's very, very
confident, come and you see, the
young man also sent a letter generated from one from Quran, what should it not be wrong,
but bank, February weekends
and metal, let me tell you about the trading profit and loss of Doctor Research
and Development Council,
I also want to say
that if you test the calls we give, then it is
for trading, you should
keep a margin of two days in it,
because the stop loss will keep peeking, so this is
for you, this is for us and you, that is
why we say that if you do
not do the population here, then if there is a stop loss in one hand, then
you will be ruined,
sir, brother, it is not important for me to say,
sir, ji Deshmukh has already said, that if 501 goes out, then
you people will keep saying that
Edison did not give the call, brother, no call, if it is
fair to me, then that is why I am telling you
that
quantum does not mean that
I am in the temple, sister, I am there, I am
with you, that is why I am telling you this  Here
I am wearing a tractor cap, whether it is an
inverter or not because
travel free mode is not a favorite for investors, you
are right but friend 10:00 absolutely perfect,
you said absolutely right that
keeping aside the others and also in terms of giving, for investment from the
28th day continuously telling you to
invest in good strokes, the
color is a matter of concern as soon as the questions come and go, but
if you are taking then it
is absolutely necessary for you to send, let's keep today's
updates for you and not even the tree, so you had
distributed the dedication for, it had become 630, had
given a bean shot, it became 254 from 266, the top has been hit,
Professor Good Godrej Consumer
Research has hit, you remember, it
gave 748 with a healthy 710 of 660, so on Friday it became
700, rate it and the Bluetooth which was
given to you in Bandhan,
it went four to five times, you
can approve it there, in front of that Reliance
Buy was given a stoploss of 8888, right now
I think that I  There is a little
over setting in this, Reliance's interest back, so the
market global realised cents were also
divided and that you Katrina has become 497
brother, the target is 110, now one day you can
book profit in the afternoon against Bandhan Bank,
you have two of my brothers, two of yours, if we start then it must be
said that for you I have no
ball 15000 1655 1800 425 and 509 and secondly
in Bank of Baroda,
which two are there where you have to buy in two and
sell in two, ICICI
Lombard, this is the buying advice for you,
from 1595 to 1602 you have to buy in loan
1575 15750 1695 target of moral force
is to buy Tata Chemicals around ₹100,
one of yours is of ₹100, you have to buy house in 102
in 498, you have to sell for 400 to 500 for Tata Chemicals
In ₹500 and here
you have an option of ₹100 and
in a copper vessel and then here you have to
invest Rs. 6464 6466 - stopper 615,
subscribe to this trick
with hotel balance, people give it to you and
send it for free after today